<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Ryan's Bike Tour - Missoula to San Francisco</title><link href="https://rjames86.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://rjames86.github.io/feeds/posts.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://rjames86.github.io/</id><updated>2016-08-19T10:34:07-07:00</updated><entry><title>Missoula to San Francisco: The Route</title><link href="https://rjames86.github.io/missoula-to-san-francisco-the-route.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-08-19T10:34:07-07:00</published><author><name>Ryan M</name></author><id>tag:rjames86.github.io,2016-08-19:missoula-to-san-francisco-the-route.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;My plan is to depart on September 7 from Missoula, MT. I’ll be following the TransAmerica route all the way to the Oregon coast where I’ll meet up with the Pacific Coast Trail and ride south all the way to San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src="//rwgps-embeds.com/routes/15762913/embed" height="500px" width="100%" frameborder="0"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My hope is that I can average roughly 100 miles a day for the entire trip, putting me at around 14 total days if I don’t stop.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Getting ready for the ride</title><link href="https://rjames86.github.io/getting-ready-for-the-ride.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-08-13T15:15:08-07:00</published><author><name>Ryan M</name></author><id>tag:rjames86.github.io,2016-08-13:getting-ready-for-the-ride.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://rjames86.github.io/photos/8bfc90a04bfeba9d1893a893b9899ddea.jpg" title="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had some free time over the weekend to see how much gear I could get on my bike. It was a good chance to see what I already had and what I still needed to buy for the trip. I already had the seat bag, and the frame bag came in the mail today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything went together nicely. The tent poles fit perfectly in the frame bag. The bag even has velcro straps specifically to hold things like this. The tent fits in the seat bag with plenty of room for other things. The sleeping bag fits up on the handlebars with plenty of room to spare, but I didn’t like how I had it strapped on. I’ll be ordering the Revelate Harness to hold it on there. You can see in the picture that the bag is pushing down on my light (which I’ve since tightened up so that shouldn’t happen).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a small bag that’ll sit on the top tube against the stem and I’m also ordering the Revelate Jerrycan that’ll also go on the top tube against the seat post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="" src="https://rjames86.github.io/photos/34a628fc1896ec3ccd56f896f920a819a.jpg" title="" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s also nice that the frame bag has a small opening in the front to allow cabling to be run through it. I have the USB cable from the Luxos U running into the bag so I can charge my phone or extra battery packs while I’m riding. I’ve also moved one of my water bottle cages to under the frame since it didn’t fit well in the triangle while the frame bag was attached.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>